Gyppers: "Eiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii! Gypper's coming out!"
GYIMI & KANO limits his sexy moves
Amazing!
I love this one!
I love this one too!
Okay, let's put this one in each.
Okay, then.
Wow.
Heh.
No, no, no.
It's like adding a little something... to hide it.
This is a project by garlic mang takina.
Uh...
Garlic Mantakina's Activity Report Special Edition
Immediately before the idol song verse contest
Idol Shinki family transcending group boundaries
Yay!
Yes, that's right.
This time, we're going to perform at Idol Uta Birthstice 2023.
Let's get to know each other in advance!
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Okay, what should we do today? Should we decide what we're going to call each other?
Sure, sure.
Nickname
Nickname I'm Yumirin
Yumirin
Yumirin today, please.
I'm Osuzu
OszOsz.
Yes, please.
I'll stay with Moe-chan.
Moe-chan
A welcome drink to show our goodwill.
Oh, wow.
Thank you very much.
It's hot today.
Soda?
With a wrinkle.
Soda.
Yay!
Then I'll stick with soda.
Yes, sir.
Cheers.
Hmm? It smells...
Hmm?
It's garlic ale, not ginger ale.
Amazing.
It's sweet despite what I've eaten.
I thought the aroma was garlic, but it's delicious.
Surprisingly good?
Yes, it's good.
I'm glad.
It's very precipitated.
It's a little scary at the bottom.
Scary.
Yes, so we're going to get to know each other in advance of the festival,Yes, that's why we decided to get to know each other in advance of the festival,
I have prepared a plan for the festival.
Here it is.
The "Meow Meow Meow Game" to fight over the arranged garlic dishes.
It's a meow meow game.
Meow Meow Game?
And when you compete for garlic dishes....
This time, I prepared 3 arranged garlic dishes that I usually eat as hospitality.
The winner of the game can choose his/her favorite dish.
You can choose. I see.
I will tell you the dishes I prepared ahead of time.
Good.
The first one is garlic egg rice.
Looks so delicious.
It's so delicious. It's a classic.
And the second one is garlic curry rice.
I guess some people would like to have this too.
It's like spicy plus garlic.
It's like savory.
It's delicious with a savory flavor. This one, too.
And the third one is garlic clam chowder.
Clam chowder.
Clam chowder has a lot of ingredients, doesn't it?
Yes, it is. It's like a white sauce, right?
That's right. Like a stew.
And here is the game we are going to play today.
Meow Meow Game.
First of all, I would like to explain the rules.
The game is played by dividing into one contestant and two respondents.
The contestant tells the word meow-meow in cat language according to the theme written on the card, and the respondent tells the word meow-meow in cat language according to the theme written on the card.
The person who gets more points within the time limit wins.The winner is the one who earns more points within the time limit.
The winner is the one with the most points after three people submit one question each.
I see. The one who can answer more questions wins.
Please answer as many questions as you can.
Yes, I understand. I understand.
I found this under the table.
What's this?
It's real.
What is it?
I haven't worn one of these for a long time.
It's a cat.
You all should wear it today and meow at Carmela.
I've never worn it.
It's so rare that I even have hands.
Now, I would like to start off with a question.
Here is the first question.
Here is the subject.
Creatures in the zoo
There are a lot of them.
Let's start!
Meow Meow Meow
Meow meow meow
Meow meow meow!
Easy!
Meow!
Nyan Meow!
Giraffe!
Oh, my gosh!
Why not?
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia miamaking out
miaow miaow miaow
miaow bear (any bear of family Rhynchogylidae)
nyan nyan nyan nyan
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia
panda
LOL
food
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia
Ah! Simpangy!
There you go.
There's a genius too.
miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow
meow meow
panda
Yay!
er, how many more are there?
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow!
Olarutan!
Meow meow meow meow meow!
Ya-ya-ya!
Nya nya nya nya.
Miramingo.
Pass!
Meow meow meow.
Tiger.
Cheetah?Cheetah?
It's over!
It's so hard!
It's got to be something unique to understand it.
I can't tell if it's too short.
Strong!
Weak!
Four points and one point.
Yes!
You didn't answer more, did you?
A lot. I did say a lot.
Next, the bell, please.
Here is the subject
The title of a Ghibli movie.
Wow!
Wow, that's hard! It's limited!
Let's start!
My favorite
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
What? Wait a minute.
My favorite
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
A thousand and one divine
Wow!
I like this one too.
meow meow meow meow meow meow
The Wind Rising
Can you do anything but this?
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meowMeow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
Hey, I fixed it.
meow!
meow meow meow meow!
Oh, hey!
Now you're getting it!
I see!
I've got to do this!
I had to do this much!
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, now go ahead and do it!
Great momentum!
That was the best cello ever!
And then...
Nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya
Well, I didn't get it!
Wait a minute!
Nyanya nyonya nyonya nyonya
I don't know how Yol moves!
Oh, my gosh!
squishy squishy!
Cat mom
meow meow meow!
Chiki Yudo
squishy squishy squishy
Nyanya nya nya nya!
LOL!
Nyanya nya nya nya nya
Lately?
squishy squishy
squishy squishyNyonya Nyonya Nyonya Nyonya
Correct.
Ah!
The last one is Red Pig.
Yes, yes, yes...
That's great.
The response rate is surprisingly high!
Next is Chaamoe-chan's
Yes!
My subject is
Jang! Wow!
Quick word!
I wonder what kind of dead thing it is...
I wonder what kind of dead
Shan Inującue
ana hello
ana
No, I do not have because I'm down
I can not say re Не get
Now don't go ılar
Nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah nyah
Tokyo Patent Kyoku Kyoku Kyoku
Nya!
Nyah courses!
What?
Nya course
serely
meow
course serely
Sleeping children grow upSleep brings up a child well
I don't care about you.
You and you are both mine
We're kinda alike
We ate together
There's a gnat, gnat, gnat bird
na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Raw gummi, raw rice, raw egg
na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
red pajamas blue pajamas
ta-da!
The end
That's great!
You got it all figured out.
So, first place goes to Moe-chan!
Second place goes to Yumeli
Third place goes to Osubu
It was pretty even.
Good competition
It was fun.
It looked like fun.
It was fun, but I'm afraid of what comes after.
You're already thinking about the next one
So, Moe, the first place winner
You can choose one of the first dishes we did.
You can have a meal
Rice with egg
Yes, that's right.Yes, it is.
Absolutely delicious.
Then I'll have curry and rice.
It's really good.
I love curry.
So then...
Clam chowder.
Okay, let's eat!
Looks so delicious!
And now I'd like to make it even better.
You can see it right in front of you, ladies and gentlemen.
Nick tube.
You're not supposed to eat it like this, are you?
No, you can't.
Then let's open it up over here.
Uh...
This way.
Let's put this in each one.
Okay, then.
No, no, no...
It looks like cheese.
It's not cheese.
It's garlic.
A little bit.
It's like you add a little bit.
Like a secret ingredient.
It's a garlic man-takino project.
Let's open it.
Let's open it.Let's open it.
Oh, wow.
Looks delicious.
Wow, the color is so nice!
Finally, add the garlic.
Add some garlic.
It's got a pretty big mouth.
Oh, wow!
It's about the size of a dried fish.
It's cute.
It's a little full.
Here you go.
about the size of a rice pudding
I'll read this once I've mixed it.
If you want to add more, I'll add more.
Okay, Mai-chan, you start.
I'll have the garlic egg rice.
Here you go.
That's a lot of garlic.
I can smell it already.
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's so good!
Wow! It's delicious!
What? The saltiness of the garlic mixed with just the right amount of
and the egg mellows it out.
Wow!
I totally get it!
It's so good!
Amazing! I've eaten a lot.
I've eaten a lot of garlic.I had one where there was totally garlic.
It's so good!
So good! I'm so happy!
Oh! Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Delicious! Yummy!
Crunchy.
Okay, I'll eat the curry.
Yes!
There's a lot of curry in it.
I'll mix it.
Yes, mix it.
The color is totally different from the first one.
It's so much lighter.
It's like a sweet curry.
Oh, yes, indeed.
Here we go.
It's good.
Delicious.
A little spicy curry combined with a hint of garlic
It's so delicious!
It's a classic!
Kind of a classic.
I don't know if it's "royal" but...
I'm curious.
Last but not least, tin
Gram chowder with garlic.
There's a lot of people here.
Lots of clumps.
Lumps.Clumps
Better mix it up.
Bon appétit!
Oh, it smells so good!
Delicious.
It's good? Is it good?
It's so delicious.
I'm so glad.
It's true.
It's true. It's true.
It's really delicious.
But if you ask me, I eat it with garlic toast or something,
Love is good.
So that's what I mean.
Seriously.
You definitely thought it was a punishment, both of you.
It's hospitality, you know.
Seriously?
It's delicious.
I can't stop.
I'm so happy.
We're all going to perform at the Songbirth Festival as a group,
Is there anything you want people to pay attention to?
I don't know. I don't know, but I think the theme of this year's festival is a fusion of the real and virtual worlds,
So I thought of something that people can enjoy both in real and virtual space.
That's wonderful.
It is the first time to touch such a metaverse-like space.
So I guess everyone is our first avatar.
It's like we can touch each other in that space.
Fans are avatars, too.It means that the fans are avatars, too.
We will be able to touch each other at close range as avatars.
It will be the first time for us to do such a thing, so they will be able to see us for the first time.
That's why we are going to perform at the Idol Song Birth Festival.
You can't miss the hot performances that you can only see here, and dream collaborations that transcend the boundaries between groups.
For more details, please check the outline column. We are waiting for you at the venue.
Come and see us.
Se-no, right or left?
Right!
Ta-da!
Tofu!
I'd like to take a why-why picture with the three of us
Why do you want to take a picture of the three of us?
Yes!
Why why why?
Why, why, why?
Why why?
This is delicious.
Yum! Yum!
It's so good.
I'm so sorry I doubted you.
I'm really sorry.
I really am.
Yes, I am.